

**O**9014406311

✓ Lifecamp FCT-Abuja

### **Skills**

- Management Support
- Excellent orator with great communication skills
- · Record and File Management
- Problem Solving and analytical thinking
- Data entry
- · Expert attention to detail
- · Social media management
- · Organizational skill
- · Problem-solving
- WordPress (web design)
- Data visualization
- · Canva graphics
- Result Interpretation
- · Data Collection and Analysis
- · Project Reporting
- · Time Management
- Strategy Development
- · Work Planning and Prioritization

## **Education & Training**

**Hubspot, Online, -** Social Media Marketing

2023

 Developing social media strategy, Social Media Listening and Monitoring, Building a Content Strategy, Social Media Advertising, and Measuring ROI.

## **Google, Online, -** Data Analytics Professional

2022

 Completed hands-on experience with data cleaning, data visualization, Interpreting and communicating data analytics findings.

### Federal College of Land Resources Technology, Owerri

Computer Science, HND 2016 – 2018.

Federal College of Land Resources Technology, Owerri Computer Science, OND 2012 – 2014.

# Nduagwa Okechukwu

## **Summary**

Motivated Administrative Officer with 5 years of experience offering office support in Non-profit association, government and education industry. Energetic and reputable individual possessing strong work ethic, professional demeanor and superb initiative. Exceptional customer service and decision-making skills.

### **Experience**

# Healthy Environment for International Development - Data Analytics Associate

Enugu, Nigeria

01 / 2022 - 12 / 2023

- · Administered guestionnaires and collation of feedback.
- Prepared checklist for project monitoring and evaluation.
- Monitored projects to ensure they comply with funders requirements.
- Developed and implemented advanced statistical models to analyze customer behavior, identify trends, and make recommendations.
- Created interactive dashboards for executives to effectively visualize key performance indicators.

### Putdabeat Records - WordPress Designer (Remote)

Richmond, USA

01 / 2021 - 12 / 2021

- · Designed and implemented WordPress websites for client.
- Ensured the design was optimized for mobile devices.
- Troubleshot WordPress issues related to themes, plugins, widgets, and content management systems.

### **Hez-Dike Secondary School - Computer Instructor**

Awka, Nigeria

01 / 2020 - 12 / 2020

- Taught over 100 students with google-meet and how to utilize different PC applications.
- Assisted in the development of online courses, such as lectures and assignments.
- Instructed classes on topics including computer hardware, operating systems, basic programming languages, basic web design and content creation.
- · Provided technical support to students and staff on various software programs.

#### **Anambra Internal Revenue Service - Data Entry Officer**

Awka, Nigeria

06 / 2018 - 12 / 2019

- · Researched and updated customer records in database system.
- Inputted data into various software programs accurately and efficiently.
- Entered large volumes of information into spreadsheets quickly and accurately.
- · Created detailed reports on data entry activities.

### Seal Development Company - Admin Associate

Abuja, Nigeria

11 / 2014 - 12 / 2015

- · Assisted in scheduling meetings and preparing agendas for executive staff.
- Provided clerical support such as answering phones, responding to emails, filing documents, copying and scanning materials.

#### References

Available upon request.